One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Let's go! Shining! Running! Forever!
Keep pushing forward!
The bond that joins us will never break
and its light will shine on the end of our dreams.
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Freedom is our only compass we need. -We are best friends-
We'll be the ones to carve out our own route.
We spend all our days moving full speed ahead, -Go east, Go west-
each day brings something new and we leave nothing unfinished.
Every trial we overcome brings a chance for thrills. (I can't stay)
Tomorrow and each day after will be heated, intense.
A chain of excitements!
That's right! Shining! Running! Forever!
Trust your curiosity, follow your heart
and head for your goal, that's what adventure is all about!
Let's go shining! Running! Forever!
Spread open the chart of your dreams!
There's power hidden in the bond between us,
it'll help us grasp the end of our dreams.
Never! Never! Never! Never stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Onward!! Army of Rogues
Hey, stop it, Straw Hat!
Pica-sama is very sensitive about his voice!
If he loses his cool when he's in that form...
Run!
You can't even call that a punch!
The whole town's coming down on us!
I'm sensing something really awful here.
Isshou-san, you have to get out of here!
It's a stone giant!
Luffy, will you stop provoking the enemy already?!
See? You're laughing too!
You two...
Here it comes!
Where are we?
"Plaza" Outside of
the Colosseum
Dunno.
It seems we're pretty far away from the palace.
Damn that rock-merging man.
He's even bigger than Oars.
If only I knew how to beat him.
Straw Hat...
Cabbage!
Pirate Hunter Zoro...
And Trafalgar...
Law!
Give me back my...
popularity, you damn Worst Generation!
What are you doing?!
He's part of my crew now!
Like hell I am!
What, do you still hate me?
No, I won't target the Straw Hat Pirates anymore.
Because my life was saved by your crewmate, God Usopp.
Yes, I will never forget his bravery as he disregarded himself to save many people.
Even though I didn't see it.
I love hearing nice things about my crew.
Ah yes...
Trafalgar, this is your hat, is it not?
I found it in front of the Colosseum.
Allow me to put it back on.
Now, step forward.
Like I'd trust you!
Well, whatever...
I'm quite busy right now.
In order to repay you all, I've decided to kill Doflamingo.
What?!
Leave it all to me.
You lot should go hide somewh-
Don't bother. I'm gonna do it.
I have to repay my debt to Rebecca for buying me lunch.
You're fighting because of food?!
As if! Don't lie to me.
You want to beat Doflamingo and gain even more popularity, right?!
What popularity?!
Just think about it.
If I defeat a pirate as evil as Doflamingo, the reporters won't leave me alone!
Mornings would begin with a rush of interviews.
"Good day, superstar."
"I'm honored to be called a superstar, so what can I do for you?"
"Cavendish-san, could you give us a few words about your pirate life in recent years?"
"Ah, are you still there, Cavendish-san?"
"What's wrong, I'm right in front of you."
"Is that so?"
"It's so bright that I can't see you!"
"Is it too bright? I'm sorry, but I just can't hide this sparkle of mine!"
"Amazing, you're really a star!"
Alrighty, let's go.
"Now, burn it into your eyes! I'm a superstar!"
Where is he?
Find him!
We can't find Straw Hat's corpse!
He was either smashed to bits or sent flying off somewhere.
Find him!
If he's still alive, let me know!
I won't let you get to Doffy!
So this is where you were hiding, Straw Hat.
Out of the way!
You're in the way!
That voice...
Wait, grandson of Garp!
Happou Navy (Gang)
Don Chinjao
We've been looking for you, you bastard!
Happou Navy (Gang)
Leader, Sai
Second in Command, Boo
I won't let you get away!
I knew it!
Wait!
This is bad, let's run!
What's up with you!
Why do you run?
They just won't quit!
Wait!
Damn you're annoying!
Why do you not wait?!
Head-Armor!
Didn't you hear me, grandson of Garp? I told you to wait!
Don't misunderstand my intentions, grandson of Garp.
My grudge against your family has long since disappeared.
Really?
We originally came here to destroy Doflamingo's business.
We don't give a shit about some bounty.
That chump change won't force us into action.
Yes, and I have decided that by beating Doflamingo to a pulp,
I can return the favor to you and God Usopp.
No, I'm gonna beat Doflamingo.
What?!
Are you trying to snub my good will?!
Warrior of Elbaf
Hajrudin
There you are, Straw Hat Luffy.
Let us forget what happened during our match.
On my pride as a warrior of Elbaf, I shall defeat Doflamingo and repay my debt to you.
My Prodence Kingdom is indebted to King Riku.
King of Prodence
Elizabello the Second
I shall be the one to defeat Doflamingo!
Strategist, Dagama
What he said, we have no interest in the bounty.
No, the ones to beat him will be us!
I shall never forget...
Jeet & Abdullah
the light from the heavens that God shone upon me!
Let us repent!
Wait up, I shall be the one to to defeat Doflamingo!
Fleet Admiral
Orlumbus
Destructive Cannon Ideo
Destruction shall be my method of repayment!
Beheader
Suleiman
His execution shall be left to me.
No, I'll be the one to kill Doflamingo!
Blue Gilly from the Long Leg Tribe
A lot of them have come out.
Don't forget about me!
Another annoying one is here.
Then what about this?
We'll beat up Doflamingo, and you guys can support us.
What are you on about, I'll defeat Doflamingo!
I said I'd be the one to do it!
It's no use.
These guys have too much pride.
You guys...
All of you, give it a rest!
I told you I'd be the one to beat Doflamingo!
What did you say?!
I told you we're repaying our debt.
If you keep spouting crap, I'll kill you, stupid benefactor!
That's right!
Honor!
Popularity!
Pride!
King Riku!
God!
A spear?!
We found them.
You guys give us a hand.
There's a two hundred million and two three hundred million bounties.
Those guys were the toys that were with us underground.
They have quite the gall!
Capture them!
Go to hell, you ungrateful bastards!
Let's go.
Yeah.
Ucy!
A bull?
I got an idea.
There's something in the smoke!
A-A bull?!
Go!
He's here!
Pica-sama, we've found him!
It's the Straw Hat Pirates!
They've returned here!
Don't let them get away!
They're riding a bull. It's those three from before.
And four, five, six... seven.
Wait, Straw Hat!
I told you all to stop following me!
Th-Their numbers... are increasing!
I'll be the one to kill Doflamingo!
Shut up!
I'll take him out, even if I have to kill all of you to do it!
What are you talking about. I'll do it!
No, I will!
Why do they suddenly have more allies?!
How should I know!
They're all participants from the Colosseum!
Whether it's three or three hundred people, it makes no difference!
Here it comes!
Hasshoken Secret Technique!
Drill Dragon
It might not be fully charged...
Light version...
King Punch!
...Drilling Nail!
Pica-sama's hand!
At this rate we'll be the ones to defeat Doflamingo!
Stop following me already!
Shut up, you damn savior!
What did you all say?!
All flash and no bang.
There is nothing my drilling head cannot break!
That was close!
Go, Ucy! To the palace!
Don't get squashed! I'm counting on you, Ucy!
Hey. Didn't I tell you to stay away?
Get off Ucy's back!
Please don't be that way.
Please, Straw Hat-san!
Ucy, I'm counting on you!
Hey! Don't let them pass!
They're headed for the palace!
I'll take you on!
Ideo, the King of Martial Arts?!
Don't let Straw Hat escape!
Don't get distracted.
Destructive Cannon!
Wanna stop me? Then bring in some stronger men!
What's with these guys?
A-Admiral Orlumbus!
This is my path!
Admiral...
Hug!
Now! Fire!
Beautiful Sword!
Swan Lake!
Look up!
Another punch is on the way!
He's so persistent!
Want another-?!
Drop it, you two!
He can restore his broken arms.
If you fight him without knowing his capabilities, you'll just waste your energy.
Then what should we do?
In that case...
Run!
And you call yourself a strategist?! Come up with a better plan!
Hush! Running is a perfectly viable strategy!
Get the hell out of here!
We can't go straight forward. Our only hope is to find a way around.
That guy is such a pain.
We can't reach the palace unless we stop him.
Hey, where did Straw Hat go?
I don't see him!
Was he crushed along with the buildings?!
There he is!
This is a shortcut! Alright!
He's on him?!
Go, Ucy!
What?!
Is he insane?!
Don't steal my thunder!
I don't believe it.
Now let's keep going to the palace!
Yeah! Go, Ucy!
Hey.
Yes?
Don't you "Go!" me!
Get off! You're too heavy for Ucy!
Oh, of course.
Pardon the late introduction. I'm Jeet.
And the big guy behind me...
My name is Abdullah.
I didn't ask!
Straw Hat!
He's freaking pissed!
I won't let you get near Doffy!
His arm!
Straw Hat-san?!
Rubber...
Grizzly Magnum!
He did it!
He smashed him?!
Pica-sama!
He did it!
Awesome, Straw Hat-san!
Great job!
Alright, now let's hurry to the palace!
Luffy, the head you just smashed was nothing but stone!
Huh?!
We're just running on a statue now.
Did he disappear again?
His real body is right ahead!
Huh? That's the stone-guy?
First time I've seen him looking like a human being.
He's got a huge sword!
Dodge!
If you can't dodge him, then stop!
We won't make it!
The bull is flying?!
That voice is so funny!
Straw Hat!
Here he comes again!
We're going ahead!
What?
Sure! I got this!
Amazing!
Get out of my way!
That's God's crew for you!
Zoro, I'm counting on you!
I'll go send Doflamingo flying!
Roger that, Captain.
I have unfinished business with Straw Hat. Move!
My captain has no business with a pebble like you.
You'll have to settle for me, you oversized soprano.
Hey, the monster stopped moving. Is he dead?
No, I doubt it.
But if it means his bothersome punches have stopped, then this is our chance!
I will take down Doflamingo!
No, I will!
Alright! Keep going, Ucy!
Yeah, do your best, bull!
Bull!
How long are you gonna hang around?! Get off!
Oh, stop it, Straw Hat-san!
Hey, Straw Hatter.
Huh?
I understand that we have no choice but to fight.
I've made up my mind.
The plan I first suggested was an indirect way to crush Doflamingo.
But to be honest, I, too, wanted to take him down directly.
I lost earlier, but this time I'll get him!
Thirteen years ago, someone very dear to me...
was killed by Doflamingo.
His name was Corazón.
He was a top commander in the Donquixote Family.
Huh?! He was one of Mingo's men?!
That's right. I owe my life to him.
He was also...
Doflamingo's little brother!